A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 36 FA307
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 36
1924-1981
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA307
12.5 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
Approximately 3,150 prints
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
File Plan note
Former Classification: P/1067
Other Finding Aids
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: blueprints, photographs, and maps. Images document the Harkness Family, Harkness House, Harkness Fellows. This series also contains a variety of material separated from the body of the early Commonwealth Fund grant records including grants in public health, rural hositals and disease research (FA290 Commonwealth Fund Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1) as well as the Division of Publications (FA285 SG 1, Series 13).
Arrangement
Arranged in subseries primarily by Format - Albums, Prints, and Materials Separated from Commonwealth Fund Grants and the Division of Publications.
Mental health; Medical research; Medical education; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Medicine, Rural; Law; Hygiene; Legal research; Legal issues; Child mental health; Child psychology; Child welfare; Education, Rural; Public welfare; Public health; New York (State); New York (N.Y.); War relief; United States; Photographs
- Albums, 1925-1942; 360 prints
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellows, 1925-1927, 1926-1928, 1927-1929; 59 prints (Box 64)
    Scope and Contents
    Including third-year fellows
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellows, 1928-1930, 1929-1931, 1931-1932; 78 prints (Box 65)
    Including third-year fellows and service fellows.
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellows, 1931-1933, 1932-1934, 1933-1935; 88 prints; Including third-year fellows and service fellows. (Box 66)
  - Commonwealth Fund Fellows, 1934-1936, 1935-1937, 1936-1938; 65 prints (Box 67)
    Including service fellows
  - Home Civil Service Fellows, 1937-1938, 1938-1939; 1 print (Box 68)
  - Ordinary Fellows, 1937-1939, 1938-1940, 1939-1941, 1940-1942; 61 prints (Box 68)
  - Service Fellows, 1937-1939, 1938-1940, 1939-1941; 8 prints (Box 68)
- Prints, 1927-1978; 2,000 prints
  - Harkness Fellowships - Fellowship Application Photographs - Fellows - A-Z, Approximately 500 prints (Box 60)
  - Harkness Family Photographs, undated; Oversized Prints - 65. Negatives - 13. (Box 61, Box 62)
    Scope and Contents note
    boats, group portraits, Harkness family, Houses, weddings, children
  - Harkness Family - Houses, undated; Oversized Prints - 2 (Box 62)
    Commonwealth Fund buildings, Houses, Architectural details
  - Edward H. Harkness Portrait, 1 portrait, approximately 200 copies. (Box 69)
  - Portraits used in Annual Reports, 1927-1941; 43 prints (Box 70)
  - Early Harkness Fellows, 1934-1937; 9 prints (Box 71)
  - House at 35 Portman Square, New York City, 4 prints (Box 71)
  - Christmas Party, 1953; 27 prints (Box 71)
  - 1 East 57th Street, New York City - First Office of the Commonwealth Fund, 1919-1925; 1 print (Box 72)
  - Harkness House - 1 East 75th Street, New York City, 13 prints, including framed print (Box 72)
  - Harkness House - Color Slides of Interior, taken by Jon G. Fox, 1978; Approximately 40 slides (Box 72)
  - Harkness House - Interiors, 13 prints (Box 63)
  - Staff Portraits, 20 prints. Also includes negatives. (Box 73)
  - Rural Hospitals - Ada, Oklahoma - Blueprints - Farm Equipment, undated; Prints - 7 (Box 57, Folder 691)
    Construction
  - Rural Hospitals - Ada Oklahoma - Photos removed from 2.5-9-A Aux, undated; Prints - 13 (Box 57, Folder 692)
    Hospitals, Construction
  - Rural Hospitals - Beloit, Kansas - Blueprints from Hospital Proper, undated; Prints - 15 (Box 57, Folder 693)
  - Rural Hospitals - Beloit, Kansas - Photos Publicity and Hospital, undated; Prints - 3 (Box 57, Folder 694)
    Hospitals
  - Rural Hospitals - Bristol, Va/Tenn - Blueprints from building/Equip, undated; Prints - 6 (Box 57, Folder 695)
  - Rural Hospitals - Bristol, Va/Tenn - Photos from Hospital Proper Anex, undated; Prints - 11 (Box 57, Folder 696)
  - Rural Hospitals - Farmville, Va - Blueprints from equipment and Bldg, undated; Prints - 13 (Box 57, Folder 697)
  - Rural Hospitals - Farmville, Va - Photos Hospital and Building, undated; Prints - 7 (Box 57, Folder 698)
  - Rural Hospitals - Glasgow, Kent - Blueprint Hospital and Photos, undated; Prints - 4 (Box 57, Folder 699)
  - Rural Hospitals - Kingsport, Tenn - Blueprints, undated; Prints - 16 (Box 57, Folder 700)
  - Rural Hospitals - Kingsport, Tenn. - Photos from building R., undated; Prints - 45 (Box 57, Folder 701)
  - Rural Hospitals - Lancaster, South Carolina - Blue Prints and Maps, 1941-1944; Prints - 6 (Box 58, Folder 702)
  - Rural Hospitals - Lancaster, South Carolina - Photos, 1940; Prints - 47 (Box 58, Folder 703)
    Hospitals, Construction, Trains
  - Rural Hospitals - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Blueprints, undated; Prints - 20 (Box 58, Folder 704)
  - Rural Hospitals - Mt. Pleasant, Michigan - Photos, undated; Prints - 560 (Box 58, Folder 708)
  - Rural Hospitals - Murfreesboro, Tenn - Blueprints, undated; Prints - 7 (Box 58, Folder 705)
  - Rural Hospitals - Murfreesboro, Tenn - Photos, undated; Prints - 13 (Box 58, Folder 706)
  - Rural Hospitals - Pittsfield, Illinois - Blueprints and Maps, undated; Prints - 13 (Box 58, Folder 707)
  - Rural Hospitals - Pittsfield, Illinois - Photos, undated; Prints - 51 (Box 58, Folder 709)
  - Rural Hospitals - Provo, Utah - Blueprints and Maps, Prints - 18 (Box 59, Folder 710)
  - Rural Hospitals - Provo, Utah - Photos, undated; Prints - 33 (Box 59, Folder 711)
  - Rural Hospitals - Rochester Regional/Corning - Photo, undated; Prints - 1 (Box 59, Folder 712)
  - Rural Hospitals - Sikeston, Missouri - Blueprints and Maps, undated; Prints - 12 (Box 59, Folder 713)
  - Rural Hospitals - Sikeston, Missouri - Photos, undated; Prints - 71 (Box 59, Folder 714)
  - Rural Hospitals - Tupelo, Mississippi - Blueprints, undated; Prints - 3 (Box 59, Folder 715)
  - Rural Hospitals - Tupelo, Mississippi - Photos, undated; Prints - 47 (Box 59, Folder 716)
  - Rural Hospitals - Wauseon, Ohio - Blueprints, undated; Prints - 6 (Box 59, Folder 717)
  - Rural Hospitals - Wauseon, Ohio - Photos, undated; Prints - 13 (Box 59, Folder 718)
- Visual Materials Separated from Grants, 1924-1981; 750 prints
  - University of Colorado (Given Institute of Pathobiology) - Preparation for a core Audiovisual Course in Pathology to Facilitate the Training of M.D.s, 4 prints (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Related Materials
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 58, Folder 544
  - American University of Beirut, 11 prints (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Grants, 6 prints (Box 74, Folder 3-4)
  - Johns Hopkins University (School of Medicine) - Program to Strengthen Johns Hopkins as a University Medical Center, 1965-1974; 9 prints (Box 74, Folder 5)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 175, Folder 1630
  - State University of New York and Pre-Service Nurse Education, Type C, Project Report by Marcia Allene Drake, Teachers College, Columbia University, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 180, Folder 1686
  - University of Hawaii (School of Medicine) - Involvement of Professional Schools in the Continuum of University Health-Sciences Education, 1976-1981; 14 prints (Box 75, Folder 7)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 139, Folder 1280
  - University of Hawaii - Study of the University's Future Role in Health Professions Education, 1970-1975; 4 prints (Box 75, Folder 8)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 75, Folder 8
  - Helpern Library of Legal Medicine - International Microfilm Journal of Legal Medicine, 1967-1970 (Box 75, Folder 9-10)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 143, Folder 1310
  - Hospice Institute for Education Training and Research, Inc. - Planning for Construction and Operation of a Model Facility for Dying Patients and Their Families, 1973-1980; 13 prints (Box 75, Folder 11)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 144, Folder 1319
  - House of the Good Samaritan - Research in Rheumatic Fever, 1935-1941; 34 prints (Box 75, Folder 12)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 146, Folder 1337
  - Hunan-Yale College of Medicine, Changsha, China (Box 75, Folder 13)
    CWF, Grants, Series 18.1, Box 147, Folder 1347
  - Hunterdon Medical Center - Consultant Service (EH), 1951; 8 prints (Box 75, Folder 14)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 148, Folder 1358
  - Institute for Muscle Research - Study of the Chemical Mechanism of Intracellular Energy Transmission, 1953-1965; 10 prints (Box 75, Folder 15-16)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 156, Folder 1441
  - Institute of International Education - Library for the Proposed Center for International Education, 1962-1966; 2 prints (Box 75, Folder 17)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 160, Folder 1481
  - Jimmy Yen's Rural Reconstruction Movement - Training of Workers in Health, 1962-1980; 3 prints (Box 75, Folder 18)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 166, Folder 1543
  - Johns Hopkins University (School of Medicine) - Program to Strengthen Selected Foreign Medical Schools - Auxiliary Reports, 1965-1968; 8 prints (Box 75, Folder 19)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 176, Folder 1635
  - University of Kentucky, 3 prints (Box 75, Folder 20-23)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Boxes 178-180, Folders 1662, 1669, 1678, 1683
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Curriculum Planning, 1958-1966; 4 prints (Box 75, Folder 24)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 182, Folder 1711
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937; 1 print (Box 75, Folder 25)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 184, Folder 1732
  - Roosevelt Hospital of New York/St. Luke's Hospital Center - Planning for the Merger of the Two Institutions, 1978-1983; 9 prints (Box 76, Folder 26)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18, Box 295, Folder 2823
  - Saskatchewan Hospital - Relation of Ward Design to Patient Behavior, 1957-1964; 8 prints (Box 76, Folder 27-28)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 301, Folder 2876-2877
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute for Cancer Research - Structure and Function of Nucleic Acids and Nucleoproteins, 4 prints (Box 76, Folder 29)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 302, Folder 2894
  - University of Southern California (School of Medicine) - Construction of Multi-discipline Teaching Laboratories, 1957-1974; 14 prints (Box 76, Folder 30-31)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1. Box 303, Folder 2901-2902
  - Southern Pediatric Seminar - General Support, 1925-1934; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 32-33)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 304, Folder 2910-2911
  - Tennessee Medical Foundation - Planning and Organizing Programs to Improve Medical Care in Selected Tennessee Communities (EHS), 1953-1959; 10 prints (Box 76, Folder 34-35)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 317, Folder 3044, 3046
  - University of Tennessee (College of Medicine) - Family General Practice Clinic (ME), 1952-1956; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 36)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 320, Folder 3073
  - Tufts University (School of Medicine) - Developmental Funds, 1961-1968; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 37)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 323, Folder 3107
  - Tulane University (School of Medicine) - Research in Schizophrenia (MR), 1950-1965; 9 prints (Box 76, Folder 38-40)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 327-329. Folders 3150, 3153, 3163
  - University of Utah (College of Medicine) - Construction and Equipment of Health Sciences Library, 1966-1971; 5 prints (Box 76, Folder 41)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 334, Folder 3212
  - University of Utah (College of Medicine) - Planning a New Medical Center, 1957-1966; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 42)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 334, Folder 3215
  - Rip Van Winkle Foundation - Mental Health Section (EHS), 1954-1964; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 43)
    CWF, Grants, Series 18.1, Box 335, Folder 3222
  - Vanderbilt University - Medical Education Program Study, 1955-1962; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 44)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 335, Folder 3229
  - Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine) - Expansion of the Department of Medicine and the Clinical Research Center, 1966-1972; 1 print (Box 76, Folder 45)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 336, Folder 3237
  - Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine) - Medical Education Program, 1961-1964; 1 print (Box 76, Folder 46)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 337, Folder 3241
  - Vanderbilt University (School of Medicine) - Syphilis Clinic, 1938; 5 prints (Box 76, Folder 47)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 337, Folder 3243
  - Virginia State Medical Society - Postgraduate Prenatal and Postnatal Instruction, 1930-1934 (Box 76, Folder 48)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 342, Folder 3289
  - University of Virginia (School of Medicine) - Establishment of a Diagnostic Clinic at the University Hospital's Outpatient Department (ME), 1955-1956; 1 print (Box 76, Folder 49)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 342, Folder 3297
  - University of Virginia Hospital - Pediatric Department, 1924-1925; 3 prints (Box 76, Folder 50)
    CWF, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 343, Folder 3307
  - War Relief and Related Purposes - American Field Services, 1942-1945; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 51)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 344, Folder 3320
  - War Relief and Related Purposes - United China Relief, Inc, 1940-1945; 5 prints (Box 76, Folder 52)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 346, Folder 335
  - Washington University (School of Medicine) - Neural Mechanisms in the Regulation of Pituitary Thyrotropic Hormone Secretion (MR), 1955-1958; 11 prints (Box 76, Folder 53)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 350, Folder 3374
  - Washington University (School of Medicine) - Pneumonia Studies, 1943-1946; 17 prints (Box 76, Folder 54-55)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.2, Box 350, Folder 3378, 3380
  - Washington University (School of Medicine) - Trachoma Research Program, 1929-1937; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 56)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 351, Folder 3387
  - University of Washington (School of Medicine) - Region-wide Program of Medical Education in the Pacific Northwest - Quarterly Reports, 1973; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 57-58)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 355 and 356, Folder 3424 and 3434
  - University of Washington (School of Medicine) - Region-wide Program of Medical Education in the Pacific Northwest - Quarterly Reports, 1974; 10 prints (Box 76, Folder 59)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 358, Folder 3445
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Building Changes to Permit Inauguration of New Curriculum (ME), 1951-1953 (Box 76, Folder 60)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 366, Folder 3522
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Department of Physiology - Peripheral Circulation and Shock Study, 1941-1949; 4 prints (Box 76, Folder 61)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 368, Folder 3535
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation, 1953-1954; 3 prints (Box 76, Folder 62)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 370, Folder 3556
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Educational Program - Evaluation (Supplementary Reports), 1951-1956; 3 prints (Box 76, Folder 63)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 376, Folder 3606
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Health Science Library, 1963-1969; 3 prints (Box 76, Folder 64)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 376, Folder 6308
  - Western Reserve University (School of Medicine) - Leukemia Study, 1937-1947; 11 prints (Box 76, Folder 65-66)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 376, Folder 3609 and 3611
  - Yale University - Center for the Study of Human Genetics, 1974-1981; 1 print (Box 76, Folder 67)
    CWF, Grant, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 381, Folder 3659
  - Yale University (Child Study Center) - Emotional Development in Early Childhood/Personality Development - Manuscript (MR), 1953-1959; 24 prints (Box 76, Folder 68)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 382, Folder 3672
  - Yale University - Memorial for Edward S. Harkness, 1952-1956; 6 prints (Box 76, Folder 69-70)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 384, Folder 3691-3692
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Auditorium Construction (ME&CH), 1958-1964; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 71)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 384, Folder 3695
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Comprehensive Program on the National Health Problem of Trauma, 1968-1978; 2 prints (Box 76, Folder 72)
    CWF, Grants, Series 18.1, Box 385, Folder 3697
  - Yale University (School of Medicine) - Experimental Study of Cardiovascular-Renal Disease, 1946-1948; 24 prints (Box 76, Folder 73-76)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 389-390, Folder 3736-3738, 3740
  - Alderson-Broaddus College - Baccalaureate Program to Train Physicians Assistants (ME&CH), 1967-1969; 6 prints (Box 77, Folder 77)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18, Box 2, Folder 16
  - University of Colorado (School of Medicine - Child Research Council Growth Study - Richard E. Scammon's Material on Human Growth and Development Structure (Box 77, Folder 78)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18, Box 67, Folder 617
  - AMF, 4 prints (Box 78, Folder 79)
  - Division of Public Health, 5 prints (Box 78, Folder 80)
  - English Mental Hygiene Program - Miscellaneous Report, 2 prints (Box 78, Folder 81)
  - Johns Hopkins University (School of Medicine) - Harriet Lane Study of the Relation of the Endocrines to Growth and Development (MR), 1937-1942; 4 prints (Box 79, Folder 82)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 173, Folder 1612
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1948-1953; 12 prints (Box 79, Folder 83)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 193, Folder 1817
  - University of Miami (School of Medicine) - Basic Study to Improve the Processes of Medical Care for an Ethnically Diverse Population, 1971-1972; 10 prints (Box 79, Folder 84)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 200, Folder 1875
  - University of Miami (School of Medicine) - Basic Study to Improve the Processes of Medical Care for an Ethnically Diverse Population/Support Study and Improvement of Medical Care to Ethnically Diverse Populations in the Inner City, 1972-1977; 9 prints (Box 79, Folder 85)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 200, Folder 187
  - Michigan Department of Health - Pneumonia Study, 1936-1938; 4 prints (Box 79, Folder 86)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 202, Folder 1902
  - University of Montreal (School of Medicine) - Endocrine Factors in Chronic Diseases Study (ME), 1944-1950; 4 prints (Box 79, Folder 87)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 212, Folder 1988
  - Nassau County Council of Boy Scouts of America - General Support, 1950-1963; 13 prints (Box 79, Folder 88)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 217, Folder 2042
  - National Organization for Public Health Nursing - Administrative Practices of Nursing Organizations in the U.S. (Study), 1930-1933; 5 prints (Box 79, Folder 89)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 233, Folder 2202
  - New Jersey Agricultural Experiment Station - Antibiotics Study, 6 prints (Box 79, Folder 90)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 236, Folder 2247
  - New York Hospital - Psychiatric Study of Habitual Abortion (MR), 1956-1959; 4 prints (Box 79, Folder 91)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 246, Folder 2345
  - New Mexico State Department of Health - County Nursing, 1929-1933; 8 prints (Box 79, Folder 92)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 237, Folder 2255
  - New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center - Rheumatic Fever Study (MR), 1928-1945; 1 print (Box 79, Folder 93)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 246, Folder 2346
  - New York University (College of Medicine) - Department of Psychiatry and Neurology - Cerebral Function Studies, 21 prints (Box 79, Folder 94)
    CWF, Grants, SG 1, Series 18.1, Box 251, Folder 2398